<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-07-12T10:37:15+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Opportunity Inbox</title><subtitle>Bringing opportunities to students</subtitle><entry><title type="html">TED Fellowships Programme 2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/tedx.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TED Fellowships Programme 2019" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/tedx</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/tedx.html">&lt;p&gt;TED is a nonprofit devoted to spreading ideas, usually in the form of short, powerful talks (18 minutes or less). TED began in 1984 as a conference where Technology, Entertainment, and Design converged, and today covers almost all topics — from science to business to global issues — in more than 100 languages. Meanwhile, independently run TEDx events help share ideas in communities around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year, the TED Fellows program selects a new class of extraordinary thinkers and doers by open application. We look for innovators on the rise in their respective fields with a bold, original approach to their work. All applicants must be 18 years or older.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;for-further-details-check-here&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/participate/ted-fellows-program/apply-to-be-a-ted-fellow/program-faq&quot;&gt;For further details check here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apply-now-to-be-a-ted-fellow&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/participate/ted-fellows-program/apply-to-be-a-ted-fellow&quot;&gt;Apply now to be a Ted fellow.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;application-deadline-august-26&quot;&gt;Application Deadline August 26&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">TED is a nonprofit devoted to spreading ideas, usually in the form of short, powerful talks (18 minutes or less). TED began in 1984 as a conference where Technology, Entertainment, and Design converged, and today covers almost all topics — from science to business to global issues — in more than 100 languages. Meanwhile, independently run TEDx events help share ideas in communities around the world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Climate Reality Project Internship</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/tcrp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Climate Reality Project Internship" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/tcrp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/tcrp.html">&lt;p&gt;The Climate Reality Project Philippines is looking for summer interns to work in our Quezon City office!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Climate Reality Project Philippines (TCRP), a nonprofit organization founded by former US Vice President Al Gore, is dedicated to leading a global cultural movement demanding immediate action on the climate crisis by using cutting-edge communications and grassroots strategies to educate the public about the urgency and solvability of the climate crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TCRP’s Student Internship Program is an unpaid program that aims to provide undergraduate students a practical experience working in an international organization who is working to localize climate science, policy, and communication. The program can also be an opportunity for the students to be engaged in different Philippine-based climate action initiatives where they can express their activism while completing their academic requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apply-now-to-be-an-intern&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://climatereality.ph/climate-reality-project-internship-program-782/&quot;&gt;Apply now to be an intern.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Climate Reality Project Philippines is looking for summer interns to work in our Quezon City office!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Research Internship in Russia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/russia.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Research Internship in Russia" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/russia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/russia.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;research-internship-in-robotics-and-computer-science-in-russia&quot;&gt;Research Internship in Robotics and Computer Science in Russia&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Innopolis University (IU) – the first Russian university with a focus on advanced Computer Science, Robotics and its applications, invites graduate and postgraduate students from abroad to do a research internship in one of its laboratories and research units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minimum term of research internship is 2 months. Interns are free to choose the most convenient internship period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Innopolis University will provide the full administrative support: documents necessary for a visa (invitation), booking accommodation in the dormitory, orientation etc. Interns are responsible for all expenses related to accommodation (40$ a month), travel, visa, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eligibilities&quot;&gt;Eligibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Master’s degree, PhD.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good academic performance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in the chosen internship area.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English language (Russian is not required).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apply-now-on-the-university-website&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://university.innopolis.ru/en/cooperation/global/international-internships/&quot;&gt;Apply now on the University website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Research Internship in Robotics and Computer Science in Russia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PayTM Mall Campus Icon</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/paytm.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PayTM Mall Campus Icon" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/paytm</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/paytm.html">&lt;p&gt;India’s higher education system is a massive engine with 700 universities and 35,000 affiliated colleges enrolling over 20 million students every year. The country’s nation’s future leaders are groomed here, and we want to help them with an exciting and industry-focused learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paytm Mall, owned by Paytm Ecommerce Pvt. Ltd has launched Campus Icon, a six-week nation-wide programme for college students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;top-performers-will-be-awarded-internships-and-full-time-job-offers&quot;&gt;Top performers will be awarded internships and full-time job offers.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://campusicon.paytmmall.com/&quot;&gt;Apply to be a PayTM Campus Icon.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/paytm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;poster paytm&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">India’s higher education system is a massive engine with 700 universities and 35,000 affiliated colleges enrolling over 20 million students every year. The country’s nation’s future leaders are groomed here, and we want to help them with an exciting and industry-focused learning experience.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NYAToday Internship</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/nyat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYAToday Internship" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/nyat</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/nyat.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;online-internship&quot;&gt;Online internship&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NYAToday is seeking interns for their Internship Program for 2018. NYAToday is an award-winning network that has over 100,000 readers from across the world. We are committed to promoting diversity of experience, cultivating youth empowerment, and encouraging youth to become more educated about the world around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eligibilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strong passion for writing and raising one’s voice about injustices in their communities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience in writing and the journalism field&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A keen attention to detail and background in fact-checking and research&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reliable and able to submit pieces by the deadline specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;apply-on-their-website-before-july-13&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nyatoday.com/jobs&quot;&gt;Apply on their website before July 13.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Online internship</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MS Hacks 2.0</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hackathon/2018/07/12/mshacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MS Hacks 2.0" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hackathon/2018/07/12/mshacks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hackathon/2018/07/12/mshacks.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;ms-hacks---innovation-is-power&quot;&gt;MS Hacks - Innovation is Power&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Hackathon is one of the biggest event that is conducted by Microsoft Student Technical Community of LPU. The sole aim of this hackathon is to provide a competitive environment where students from all the domains come together and build something innovative. We encourage the students to build problems that can solve real-life challenges for users. We aim to build better future with Technology. Are you in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;themes&quot;&gt;Themes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobility.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AI/ML.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Big Data.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WebApp .&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Social Cause.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;register-here&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mshacks.microsoftlpu.com/&quot;&gt;Register here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lpu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;poster for ms&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">MS Hacks - Innovation is Power</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">L’Oréal For Young Women In Science Scholarship 2018</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/loreal.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="L'Oréal For Young Women In Science Scholarship 2018" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/loreal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/loreal.html">&lt;p&gt;L’Oréal India strongly believes that Science is the source of progress, and the contribution of women is vital to its future. That is why we have initiated the L’Oréal India For Young Women in Science Scholarship Programme, which encourages and supports young women to pursue careers in science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The programme was instituted in 2003 and has consistently helped young women to pursue scientific studies. A scholarship of Rs. 250,000/- each is granted to promising but economically disadvantaged young women and covers college fees for study in any scientific field in a recognized college or university in India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scholarship consists of up to Rs. 2.5 lacs, granted in equal annual instalments over the period of the degree of study, subject to the submission of proof of the candidate passing each year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till date we have given 300 scholarships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scholarship is open for study in any field of Science: Medicine, Engineering, Information Technology, Pharmacy, Biotechnology, and other graduate courses pertaining to Science (B.Sc) etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Scholarship is only for girl students desirous of pursuing a degree course in Science/ Medical/ Engineering/ Biotechnology or any other scientific field, in a recognized institute in India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;application-deadline-july-16&quot;&gt;Application deadline July 16&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foryoungwomeninscience.com/&quot;&gt;Apply for the scholarship now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">L’Oréal India strongly believes that Science is the source of progress, and the contribution of women is vital to its future. That is why we have initiated the L’Oréal India For Young Women in Science Scholarship Programme, which encourages and supports young women to pursue careers in science.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Internship at Khan Academy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/khan-academy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Internship at Khan Academy" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/khan-academy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/internship/2018/07/12/khan-academy.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;spend-a-few-months-building-free-education-for-the-world&quot;&gt;Spend a few months building free education for the world&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Khan Academy’s content is used by classrooms and individuals in over 25 languages around the world. More than 2 billion interactive math problems have been done. Our faculty’s videos have been viewed over 400,000,000 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an intern, any improvement you make can instantly help millions of students learn whatever they want, whenever they want. If this type of educational scale excites you as much as it does us, we need your help to educate the entire world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/careers/interns&quot;&gt;Apply now and to be a part of Khan Academy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Spend a few months building free education for the world</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JAPANESE GOVERNMENT (MEXT) SCHOLARSHIP</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/japan-mext.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JAPANESE GOVERNMENT (MEXT) SCHOLARSHIP" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/japan-mext</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/scholarship/2018/07/12/japan-mext.html">&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology (MEXT) of Japan offers scholarships to international students who wish to study in graduate courses at Japanese universities as Research Students (either regular students or non-regular students) under the Japanese Government (MEXT) Scholarship Program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;pplicants should apply for the field of study they majored in at university or its related field. Moreover, the fields of study must be subjects which applicants will be able to study and research in graduate courses at Japanese universities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fields of study may be restricted to particular fields by the Japanese Embassy/Consulate General (hereinafter referred to as the “Japanese diplomatic mission”) in the applicant’s country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traditional entertainment arts such as Kabuki and classical Japanese dances, or subjects that require practical training in specific technologies or techniques at factories or companies are not included in the fields of study under this scholarship program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A student who studies medicine, dentistry or welfare science will not be allowed to engage in clinical training such as medical care and operative surgery until he/she obtains a relevant license from the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare under applicable Japanese laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;for-application-and-further-details-visit-the-offical-site&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.in.emb-japan.go.jp/Education/japanese_government_scholarships.html&quot;&gt;For application and further details, visit the offical site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology (MEXT) of Japan offers scholarships to international students who wish to study in graduate courses at Japanese universities as Research Students (either regular students or non-regular students) under the Japanese Government (MEXT) Scholarship Program.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fentress Global Challenge</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/competition/2018/07/12/fretness.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fentress Global Challenge" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/competition/2018/07/12/fretness</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/competition/2018/07/12/fretness.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;airport-of-the-future&quot;&gt;Airport of the Future&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global commerce and the unprecedented demand for travel and have resulted in the proliferation of airports around the world. In their short history, terminal buildings have been criticized for employing generic architectural forms that are unapologetically disconnected from their context and cultural identity. Technical complexity and functional design have often taken precedence over quality and comfort for users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In less than a century, the airport has emerged as a new architectural typology that is as important as other large-scale public buildings such as museums, libraries, temples, and courthouses. Airports are among the most complex and highly frequented transportation hubs, but they are also increasingly important places for work, commerce, recreation, and culture. The rapid evolution of airports necessitates the incorporation of the latest developments in technology, design, and social trends around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fentress Global Challenge (FGC) competition is open to graduate and undergraduate students who are currently pursuing architecture or engineering degrees in an accredited university program, as well as recent graduates (within the last four years) with a degree in architecture or engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;register-for-the-challenge-and-innovate&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fentressglobalchallenge.com/user/register&quot;&gt;Register for the challenge, and innovate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Airport of the Future</summary></entry></feed>